《法外情真》前情回顾
Previously on The Guardian.
他们给了我你的工作
I been offered your job.
我接受了
I took it.
露露跟我说  你辞职了
Lulu told me that you... that you quit.
我要结婚了
I'm getting married.
今早跟维多利亚求婚了
Proposed to Victoria this morning.
还有  我快死了
And, I'm dying.
什么
What?
肌萎缩性侧索硬化症
ALS...
卢伽雷氏症
Lou Gehrig's disease.
这已经是我们两天里第三次约会了  杰克
Look, this is our third date in two days, Jack.
我还一点儿都不了解你呢
I don't really know anything about you.
听着  我不是同性恋
Look I'm not gay.
不是男女之间的事儿
It's not romantic or anything.
我只是想加入乡村俱乐部而已
I just wanted to join the country club...
我真的很喜欢那种  能和凯特这样的人在一起的想法
I really like the idea of being with someone like Kate...
尼克·发林  这是艾米莉·伯恩斯利
Nike Fallin, this is Emily Bernsley.
我  呃  今天给威廉姆·科特打电话了
I, uh, called William Kurt today.
他说她上周把她辞退了
And he said he fired her last week.
我真的很喜欢你们所作的事
I really like what you guys do.
- 我不希望你走  - 就因为我生病了吗
- I don't want you to go. - Because I'm sick?
因为
Because...
你无可替代
You are indispensable.
尼克
So Nick...
我在想
I was thinking...
我能往西游多远
of seeing how far west I could swim.
我快要死了  尼克
I am going to die, Nick.
我努力不去想这件事  你知道吗
I'm trying to get my mind around it, you know?
亲爱的  你把这个给忘了
Honey, you forgot this.
- 没有你我该怎么办  - 我知道
- What would I do without you? - I know.
- 照顾好自己  - 再见亲爱的
- Take care. - Bye, honey.
你好  请问需要什么帮助
Hello. Can I help you?
另外  看起来去皮特隧道的一条路
And it looks like one of the lanes of the ft. Pitt Tunnel
关闭了
inbound is closed.
所以可以的话  请绕行西区大桥
So you might want to take the West End Bridge if you possibly can.
再来看看这条新闻  又一起枪击
Now checking the news.Another shooting.
这次是在南部的一个安静郊区
This time in a quiet suburb south of the city...
今晚我要不要穿我的新衬衣呢
So shall I wear my new shirt tonight?
- 你的紫色新衬衣  - 是薰衣草色的
- Your new purple shirt? - It's lavender.
不要
no.
你今天晚上不应该穿你的紫色新衬衣
You should not wear your new purple shirt tonight.
不应该吗
No?
你不喜欢我的薰衣草色衬衫  是吗
You don't like my lavender shirt, huh?
我喜欢七十岁以上的女人穿紫色的
I like purple on women over the age of 70.
你不想这样吗
You don't want to do this, huh?
参加你的新成员晚宴吗
Attend your new members' dinner?
是的
Right.
好吧  说不定你走运  可能他们会取消之类的
Well, maybe you'll get lucky. Maybe they'll cancel it or something.
他们为什么这么做
Why would they do that?
这个  城里有个家伙瞎转悠  冷血的枪杀别人
Well, there's some guy running around the city shooting people in cold blood.
其他人的悲剧并没有阻止新教徒集会
Other people's tragedies don't prohibit the WASPs from gathering.
事实上  这只会鼓励他们
ln fact, it only encourages them.
我加入你爸爸的俱乐部  这确实很影响你  是吗
It really bothers you that I'm joining your father's club, doesn't it.
黑色鞋子配这个  不要棕色的
Black shoes with this, not brown.
早上好  有邮件吗
Morning. Mail?
这是地区检察官的传票
This is a subpoena from the District Attorney's office.
- 尼克  你有空吗  - 当然
- Uh, Nick, you have a second? - Sure.
我们还需要一些客户表格
We're gonna need some more client forms.
- 你那个课程上的怎么样  - 哪个课程
- How are you doing with that course? - What course?
- 你和维多利亚一起做的那个课程  - 应对肌萎缩性侧索硬化症
- The course you're doing with Victoria? - Coping with ALS?
- 是的  - 非常有趣  非常有娱乐性
- Yeah. - Very fun. Very entertaining.
不错
Good.
几天前我们了解到  在不久的将来
A few days ago we learned that at a certain point in the not-too-distant future,
我必须用眉毛去交流
I would have to use my eyebrows to communicate.
所以维多利亚很崩溃  我们取消了订婚
So...Victoria has a major meltdown. We kinda break om the engagement.
阿尔文
Alvin...
劳里有一个有意思案例给你
Laurie's got an interesting case for you.
孩子的名字叫安德鲁·福特
Child's name is Andrew Ford.
十天前他在他的卧室被袭击了
Ten days ago, he was attacked in his bedroom.
他被猥亵然后被刺伤了
He was molested and then stabbed.
警方觉得他爸爸是袭击者
The police think that the father was the attacker
所以社会服务想让把他从家中带走
so Social Services wants to remove him from his home.
- 他爸爸曾经被捕过吗  - 是的  但是他被保释了
- Has the father been arrested? - Yes, but he's out on bail.
劳里现在掌握了全部的细节
Laurie's, getting all the details right now.
听着  阿尔文  我对维多利亚的事情表示抱歉
Listen, Alvin, I'm sorry about Victoria.
谢谢
Thanks.
你知道的 如果有任何事情我能做的
You know, if there's anything I can do...
劳里会帮你了解情况的
Laurie will bring you up to speed.
好的
Okay.
第三季  第十九集
法外真情
翻译   七哥
校对  油 球
特效  转轮 枪
你都了解些什么
What do you got?
他爸爸的一件T恤在安德鲁的房间里被发现  上面还有精液
One of his father's T-shirts was found in Andrew's room with semen stains on it.
就在攻击发生的几个小时前
And just a few hours before the attack,
他爸爸从网站上下载了色情图片
his father downloaded pornographic images from the Internet.
- 儿童色情图吗  - 不是
- Child porn? - No.
好的  这个看起来不足以与父亲有关
Well, it doesn't seem enough to implicate the father.
没有任何强行进入的痕迹
There were no signs of forced entry.
福特先生和福特太太不再共用一个卧室  所以他没有不在场证明
Mr. and Mrs. Ford no longer share a bedroom, so he doesn't have an alibi
而且福特先生拒绝警方对安德鲁进行
and Mr. Ford refused to allow the police to conduct
性侵检查
a sexual assault exam on Andrew.
那  那孩子说了什么
What's the-- what's the kid saying?
他进医院的时候  他告诉警方
When he was in the hospital, he told the police
袭击他的人一直再重复  不要再说了
his attacker kept repeating ''Don't tell anyone.''
但是警方问他能否去指认袭击他的人  他说不要
But when the police asked him if he could identify his attacker, he said, ''No.''
现在他说他什么都不记得了
And now he says he doesn't remember anything at all.
你怎么想
What do you think?
安德鲁的前臂和手指都有防御性伤口
Andrew has defensive wounds on his forearm and his fingers.
所以我想他可能看见是谁对他做了这些
So I think he probably saw who did this to him.
好吧
All right.
好的
Okay.
安德鲁  这是尼克·法林
Hey, Andrew. This is Nick Fallin.
你好
Hi.
你怎么样
How do you do?
我必须向法院建议你应该住哪
I have to make a recommendation to the court about where you should live
直到警方把这件事情解决
while the police are sorting this thing out.
好
Okay.
所以我有些问题必须要问你
So I have to ask you a few questions.
我只想回家
I just want to go home.
好的  我理解你
Right. I understand.
你和你爸爸住在一起你不担心吗
You're not concerned about living with your father?
我真的想不起来发生了什么
I really can't remember what happened.
我没有撒谎
I'm not lying.
我真的想不起来了
I really can't remember.
好的  艾米丽  你确定你不想这个工作吗
Well, Emily, are you sure you don't want the job?
谢谢  但是不用了
Thank you for the offer, but no.
为什么不呢
Why not?
这个组织正和我看到的一样  注定要失败的
The organization is, as I see it, kind of... it's set up to fail.
阿尔文·马斯特森生病了
Alvin Masterson is ill with--
- 好的好的  - 而且你缺少律师
- Right. Right. - And you're short of attorneys.
还有你的志愿者的项目  留住尼克  基本上不存在
And your volunteer program, save for that Nick guy, it's basically non-existent.
你马上要有个宝宝了  所以
You're gonna have a baby soon, so...
这个组织  它就注定
The organization, it's set up to--
你为了一个原因来这里  是吗
You came here for a reason, right?
是的
Yeah, I did.
我觉得  看吧  我不知道为什么柯克&麦吉律所会解雇你
I mean, look, I don't know why you got fired from Kirk & McGee,
但是告诉你实话  这很有可能是我雇你的原因
but to tell you the truth, it's probably why I want to hire you.
你来这是因为你想有点影响
You came here because you want to have an impact,
你知道你会有所成就的
you know you can make a difference.
就再试着做一周
Just give it a week.
不  我现在没有时间放在这事上
Uh, no, I don't have time for that right now.
那些表格帮我找好了吗吗  谢谢
Do you have those forms for me? Thank you.
孩子那边情况怎么样
How did it go with the kid?
好吧  他说他不记得了  而且他只想回家
Well, he says he doesn't remember, and, uh, he wants to go home.
阿尔文  我们已经被传唤出庭听证会了
Alvin, we've been subpoenaed to appear at a hearing to show cause.
为什么
Why?
地方检察官想要看我们一些客户的文件客户的
The DA wants to see some of our clients' files.
跟我来
Come with me.
- 尼克  - 怎么了
- Nick? - Yeah?
- 艾米丽  - 是啊我记得
- Emily. - Yeah, I remember.
我听说福特的案子了  我想我可能能帮到你
I heard about the Ford case, and I was wondering if I might help you.
- 帮我  - 是啊
- Help me? - Right.
- 如果你需要帮助的话我很乐意  - 不用了谢谢
-lf you need some help, I'd like to- - No. Thanks.
很感谢  但是我现在还能应付的过来
I appreciate it, but I can handle it myself.
传票上面说他们想知道在1985年6月到12月之间
It says in the subpoena that they want the names of any clients
被安置到白橡树集体之家
who were placed in the White Oak group home
所有客户的名单
between June and December of 1985.
白橡树  我从来没听说过
White Oak? I've never heard of that.
那是因为他们十年就被关掉了
That's because they were shut down ten years ago.
嗯  但那之前他们是做什么的呢
Yeah, but what was it?
遭受性虐待的男孩的治疗中心
A treatment center for sexually abused boys.
为什么警方想要这些记录
And why are the police seeking the records?
传票上没说  但是我们不可能把这些交给他们
It doesn't say. But there's no way that we're handing them over.
这些孩子相信我们  露露  他们相信我们会照顾他们
These kids trusted us, Lulu. They trusted us to look after them.
- 你好卡尔  - 你好杰克
- Hi, Carl. - Hey, Jake.
给我来些薄荷糖  还有  呃
I'll get those mints. And, uh...
你只有这些花了吗
These the only flowers you got?
什么  这些对你的秘书还不够
What, they're not good enough for your secretary?
- 这些不是给我秘书的  - 不错嘛
- Oh, these aren't for my secretary. - Good for you.
我可能会  呃  要这些薰衣草
Maybe I'll, uh, get the lavender ones.
杰克  如果一个女孩子真的喜欢你  别从我这儿买
Jake, If a girl actually likes you, don't buy flowers from me.
去好的地方买
Go someplace good.
这一刀买薄荷糖
That's a dollar for the mints.
好的
All right.
谢谢了卡尔
Thanks, Carl.
法官大人  这些记录受到律师与客户之间的保密协议保护
Your Honor, these records are protected by attorney/client confidentially.
此外  这些记录是密封的
Furthermore, these records are sealed
因为他们有关未成年人的性虐待
because they concern the sexual abuse of minors.
马斯特森先生  让芬纳兰先生解释
Mr. Masterson, allow Mr. Finneran to explain.
法官大人  您的传票1985年6月到12月之间住在白橡树之家的人
Your Honor, our subpoena requests information regarding those LSP clients
有关这些LSP客户端的信息
who lived in the White Oak group home between June and December of 1985.
为什么警察对这些人感兴趣
Why are the police interested in these residents?
这有点复杂
This is somewhat complicated.
好的  尽你所能解释清楚
Well, then do your best to be clear.
那些最近被谋杀的男性  都被指控为恋童癖
Those men who were recently murdered are accused pedophiles.
据说每个人都虐待了儿童
Each had allegedly abused children in their care.
你是在说这些恋童癖住在同一个集体家庭里吗
And you're saying these pedophiles lived together in a group home?
不不不  当然不是了  法官大人  不是
No. No, no. Of course not, Your Honor, no.
这些受害者19年前都住在
The victims lived together in the White Oak group home,
白橡树之家里
19 years ago.
为什么这个让你感兴趣
Why does this interest you?
根据警探所说  一个曾住在白橡树的居民记得
According to detectives, one of the former White Oak residents
另外一个人  不停的幻想
remembers another one fantasizing, repeatedly
找到并杀了那些侵犯他们的人
about hunting down and killing their abusers.
- 哪一个  - 问题就在这儿
- Which one? - Well, this is our problem.
我们的目击者不记得名字  何况事情是在20年前
Our witness can't remember the name. It was, after all, 20 years ago.
马斯特森先生  作为儿童拥护者
Mr. Masterson, as a child advocate,
您是否需要就最利于你客户的方案行事
aren't you required to act in your clients' best interests?
是的
Yes.
有时候会需要您泄露机密信息吗
And doesn't that sometimes require you to reveal confidential information?
这没错  法官大人  但是我没看到这种情况有什么影响
Well, that's true, Your Honor, but I fail to see how this situation has any bearing--
马斯特森先生  我要求您提供这些文件
Mr. Masterson, I'm ordering you to produce these files.
- 谢谢您  法官大人  - 但是不是向芬纳兰先生提供
- Thank you, Your Honor. - But not to Mr. Finneran.
我会先查阅一下  然后决定那些警官能看
I'll review them first and then decide which of these files the police can see.
社区服务部门尝试将布兰登·福特的儿子从家中带走
Social Services is attempting to pull Brandon Ford's son from his home
这一做法  毫无根据
based on unfounded allegations.
法官大人  这些指控足以证明逮捕是正当的
Your Honor, the allegations were substantial enough to justify an arrest.
布兰登·福特没有任何不法行为
Brandon Ford is innocent of any wrongdoing,
而且我们相信这项指控将在即将举行的
and we believe the charges will be dismissed
初步听证会上被驳回
at the upcoming preliminary hearing.
我们所要求的是把安德鲁送到寄养中心
All we're asking is that Andrew be placed in foster care
直到对他父亲的指控得到解决
until the charges against his father are resolved.
法官大人  安德鲁想要回家
Your Honor, Andrew wants to go home.
情况属实吗  法林先生
ls that true, Mr. Fallin?
是的
Yes.
你的建议是什么
And what is your recommendation?
福特先生要么离开家  同意接受监督探视
Either Mr. Ford should leave the home and agree to supervised visits
要么把安德鲁送去寄养中心
or Andrew should be placed in foster care.
法官大人  我能冒昧说一句吗
Your Honor, may I speak?
我没有伤害我儿子
I didn't hurt my son.
我被指责了一些  我永远都不会去做的事情
I'm being blamed for something I would never do.
我去哪都会有报纸报道这件事情
Everywhere I go, newspapers are writing about this.
人们会打电话到我家并且威胁我
People are calling my house and threatening me.
我爱我的儿子  而且我想照顾他
And I love my son, and I want to take care of him.
我并没有做这件事情
And I didn't do this.
我没有做
I did not do this.
安德鲁将住在寄养中心  直到刑事指控得到解决
Andrew will live in foster care until the criminal charges are resolved.
你们有安排吗  索尔特女士
Do you have a placement, Ms. Solt?
我们有  谢谢你法官大人
We do, Your Honor. Thank you.
我们走吧
Let's go.
没关系的
It's all right.
什么
What?
你想要一点咖啡吗
Do you want some coffee?
我不用咖啡因的
I don't use caffeine.
尼克
Nick.
我刚接到地方检察官办公室关于福特案子的电话
I just got a call from the District Attorney's office about the Ford case.
原来t恤上的DNA被污染了
It turns out that the DNA on the t-shirt is contaminated,
而且他们觉得色情片的证据是不足够的
and they think the pornography is gonna be inadmissible.
所以他们想让安德鲁后天在他父亲的
So they want Andrew to testify at his father's preliminary hearing
初步听证会上作证
the day after tomorrow.
否则法官会驳回这个案子的
Otherwise the judge is gonna throw the case out.
- 好的  我会跟安德鲁谈谈的  - 好
- All right. I'll talk to Andrew. - Okay.
- 阿尔文  - 劳里
- Alvin. - Hey, Laurie.
- 我想有空和你谈谈  - 当然可以
- I'd like to talk to you sometime. - Of course.
- 我看我能做什么吧  - 谢谢你
- See what I can do. - Thank you.
你有空吗
You have a second?
有  进来吧
Yeah, come on in.
地方检察官的理论是  在城市里到处开枪射击的人
The DA has a theory that the person going around the city shooting people
是性虐待的受害者
was the victim of sexual abuse.
真的吗
Really?
这就是他传唤我们以前的客户的原因
That's why he subpoenaed the records of our former clients.
哦  好的
Oh. Okay.
好的
Okay?
这是对受虐儿童反应的扭曲
This is a distortion of how an abused child reacts.
这是毫无根据  颠倒黑白的
It's unfounded and it's invasive.
- 好吧  法官怎么说  - 那法官是个弱智
- Well, what does the judge say? - The judge is an idiot.
她对虐待儿童问题毫无经验
She has no expertise regarding child abuse issues,
没有对复杂事物的理解
no understanding of the intricacies.
但是艾尔文  如果法官命令我们交出文件的话
But, Alvin, if the judge ordered us to hand over the files--
- 这是政治迫害  露露  - 那我们就把文件交出来
- It's a witch hunt, Lulu. - Then we hand over the files.
交出这些记录是对受害者的惩罚
Handing over these records punishes people for being victimized.
- 艾尔文  - 你看  这些男性中的一个是前职业运动员
- Alvin-- - Look, one of these men
前职业运动员
is a former professional athlete
他从来没有把自己的遭遇公之于众
who never went public with what happened to him.
另外一个男性被他父亲严重虐待过
Another is a man who was so badly abused by his father
他最后脑部受伤了
that he ended up with a brain injury.
对不起  我没打断什么吧
Oh, I'm sorry. Was I interrupting something?
没有没有  怎么了
No, no. What's up?
你知道那个孩子吧  他爸爸因为刺伤他被起诉
You know the kid whose father was charged with stabbing him?
- 知道  安德鲁·福特  - 对
- Yeah. Andrew Ford. - Right.
对他爸爸不利的证据被推翻了
The evidence against his father has been thrown out,
所以地方检察官希望安德鲁作证
so the DA wants Andrew to testify.
所以问题所在是什么
So what's the problem?
安德鲁撒谎了
Andrew's gonna lie on the stand.
好吧  你认为你该指控他证词的真实性吗吗
Well, do you think you should challenge his competency?
好吧  如果成了的话  他就直接回他爸爸那里了
Well, if that works then he's straight back with his father.
没错  你认为他爸爸袭击他了吗
Right. And you think that his father attacked him?
我觉得袭击了
Yeah, I do.
露露  我一个小时之内  就得提交这些资料
Lulu, I gotta hand these papers over in an hour.
艾尔文  我们没有根据对法官的判决提出上诉
Alvin, we do not have the resources to appeal the judge's decision.
你是在强迫我吗
Are you forcing me to do this?
你知道的  如果这样能让你感觉好一点  那么是的
You know, if it makes you feel better, then, yes,
请交出这些文件
I'm ordering you to hand over the files.
怎么了
What is it?
宝宝刚踢了我一下
The baby just kicked.
嗨  阿尔文
Hey, Alvin?
法官那边儿怎么样
How did it go with the judge?
我得上交那些才叫了
I have to hand over the records.
我可以帮你找
I could help you look for them.
看你能不能找到查尔斯·兰伯特和威廉·亨森
See if you can find Charles Lambert and William Henson.
不是有一个橄榄球运动员叫查尔斯·兰伯特吗
Wasn't there a football player named Charles Lambert?
是的
Yeah.
他是个很大只的人  我记得大  他很壮
He was a big guy. I remember him. He's huge.
这是其他两个文件
Here are those other two files.
约翰·罗斯
John Rose.
被他叔叔强暴了
Raped by his uncle
然后在我安置他的第一个集体之家里  被一个比他大的男孩猥亵
and then molested by an older boy in the first group home I placed him in.
我不明白提起这个  是对警察有什么帮助
I don't see how bringing this up helps the police at all.
我把亨森准备好
I'll get the Henson file ready.
我叔叔他迫使我
My uncle, he made me.
我叔叔让我做这些事情
My uncle made me do those things.
他告诉我  我必须这么做
He told me I had to.
他告诉我如果我不的话  我会有麻烦
He told me I was in trouble if I didn't.
我不是说  我叔叔对我做了什么
I'm not saying that what my uncle did to me
没有改变我的生活
didn't change my life.
但是我已经处理好了
But I dealt with it.
我叔叔有问题  而且他从来不接受
My uncle had a problem, and he never came to terms with it.
他  呃
He, uh...
他死的时候都没承认他做过什么
He died without ever admitting what he'd done.
但是那是他需要背负的罪孽  不是我的
But that's his cross to bear, it's not mine.
约翰
John...
我们的政策是在  必须披露机密信息时  要通知客户
It's our policy to inform people when we must reveal confidential information.
马斯特森先生  我不活在过去
Mr. Masterson, I don't live in the past.
所以如果告诉我这些会帮助警方办案
So if talking to me about this will help the police solve a crime,
我意思是  我明白的
I mean... I understand.
好吧  不要感到害怕  或者你必须和警察谈谈这件事。
Well, don't feel intimidated or that you have to talk to the police about this.
我的家庭支持着我并且理解
My family supports me and understands...
上帝看穿我们的一切
and God sees us through.
你有一个美好的家庭
You have a beautiful family.
谢谢你
Thank you.
很高兴你过的这么好
It's good to see you doing so well.
呃  或许你想留下来一起吃晚饭
Um, maybe you'd like to stay for dinner?
我不行  还有其他人我需要去通知
I can't. I have other people I need to talk to about this.
对不起打扰了
I'm sorry for the intrusion.
过去是
The past is...
对不起打扰了
I'm sorry for the intrusion.
你会给我们团队里的人说这件事吗
You gonna tell the guys on my team about this?
你不能告诉任何人
You can't tell nobody about what happened.
对不起  查尔斯  这超出我的控制了
I'm sorry, Charles. It's out of my control.
我不会给任何人说的  艾尔文  永远不
I never told nobody about this, Alvin. Never.
我明白
I understand.
- 一个和我一样的人  - 当然了
- A guy in my position. - Of course.
- 我有些新进展  这个地方不错
-I got a good thing going here. This place is going good.
我能看见
I can see that.
我还是得到了一些支持  当地的  但是他们付钱
I still got some endorsements. Local, but they pay.
好的
Right.
我不能让人们知道我继父对我做了什么
I can't have people knowing what my step-dad did to me.
我知道
I know.
- 我需要一个律师  - 他们有记录的
- I'm gonna get a lawyer. - They have the records.
也许你应该合作  把它解决掉
Maybe you should just cooperate and get it over with.
- 阿尔文  - 查尔斯  宝贝
- Alvin-- - Hey, Charles, sweetie.
我能跟你说两句吗
Can I talk to you for a sec?
宝贝
Hey, baby!
我们 一个小时就能找到承办人了
We've got the caterers in an hour.
这是谁
Um...who's this?
就是
Uh...just, um...
好吧  就是
Well, just, um...
先生你想要把这个给谁
Who did you want this made out to, sir?
- 阿尔文  - 阿尔文
- Alvin. - Alvin.
我是个大粉丝
I'm a huge fan.
- 谢谢你  - 谢谢
- Thank you. - Thank you.
好的  伴郎们  他们需要测量一下尺寸
Okay, the groomsmen, they need to get their measurements in.
查尔斯   你能着手去办吗
Charles, will you get on that?
-  好的  - 好样的
- Yes. - Okay, good.
我用轻木做的
I made it out of balsa wood.
手工室有多余的轻木
There was extra balsa wood in the craft room.
他们只是想把这些扔出去
They were just gonna throw it out.
而且你说你喜欢船
And you said you liked boats.
我  我意思是你是喜欢船的  对吧
l--l mean, you did like boats, right?
你有阵子有辆摩托艇
You had a motorboat for a while.
是啊  它在离这不远的码头里
I did. Kept it in the marina not far from here.
对 我记得
Yeah, I remember that.
比利  我来这儿的原因
So Billy, the reason I'm here.
- 你想要一个苹果吗  - 一个苹果
- You want an apple? - An apple?
我有些苹果
I got some apples.
比利  今天警察来我办公室了
Billy, the police came to my office today.
- 我有麻烦了吗  - 没有
- Am I in trouble? - No.
- 我做什么了吗  - 没  比利  不是
- Did I do something? - No, Billy. No.
那  那为什么警方因为我见你
How--how come the police came to see you about me?
他们想要你的档案
They want your records.
我  我  我不知道这什么意思
I--I don't know what that means.
他们想知道你身上发生过什么
They want to know about what happened to you,
当你还是个男孩的时候  和你爸爸
when you were a boy, with your father.
所以呢
So?
比利  重点他们会和你聊聊发生了什么
Billy, the point is they're gonna talk to you about what happened.
他们想知道所有的细节
They're gonna know all the details.
我做了什么吗
Did I do something?
没有
No.
这关乎那些被杀的男性
It's about all these men who have been killed.
男性被杀了吗
Men are getting killed?
就在城里  新闻上都是
ln the city. It's been in the news.
所以比利
So Billy...
你有工作吗
Do you have a job?
没有
No.
- 还酗酒吗  - 你呢
- Still drinking? - You?
什么
What?
你老是闻起来像苏格兰威士忌
You always smelled like scotch.
比利  不
Ah, Billy, no.
我  我再也没喝过酒
l, uh... I don't drink anymore.
那很好啊  这对你好
That's good. That's good for you.
我能问问你一些事吗
Can I ask you something?
什么
What?
好吧  我需要一些人帮我建造一些东西
Well, I need someone to help build some things for me.
什么样的
What kind of things?
斜坡  安装螺柱
Ramps, install stum.
- 你知道的  给那些人们  - 残障人士
- You know, for people like-- - Handicap stuff?
残障人士
Handicap stuff.
为什么
How come?
我  呃
l, uh...
我有这种疾病  而且我  我的生活会改变
I have this disease, and my, uh, my life's gonna change.
给  明天来我办公室  我们再聊聊
Here, come to my omice tomorrow. We'll talk about it.
如果警察过分骚扰你  给我打电话
And call me if the police hassle you too much.
好
Okay.
威廉·亨森  这里是警探德马里亚  匹兹堡警方的
William Henson? Detective DeMaria, Pittsburgh Police.
如果你有空的话  我们想要问你一些问题
We would like to ask you a few questions if you've got a minute.
- 你好  - 你好
- Hi. - Hi.
- 给  这个是给你的  - 杰克
- Oh! Here. This is for you. - Oh! Jake!
还有  好消息  你脱身了
And, uh, good news: You're off the hook.
俱乐部的人打电话来推迟了
The guy from the club called and postponed.
那个今天早上被枪击的人吗
Yeah, the man who was shot this morning?
他叫肯·格雷厄姆  他在亨普希尔·史密斯公司工作
His name was Ken Graham. He worked at Hemphill-Smith.
- 真的吗  - 真的
- Really? - Yeah.
他是这个俱乐部的会员好多年了
He's been a member of the club for years.
- 好吧你很了解他吗  - 格雷厄姆先生吗  不
- Well, did you know him well? - Mr. Graham? No.
我记得他很爱笑  而且讲一些笨笨的玩笑
I remember he used to laugh a lot and tell stupid jokes.
我认识他儿子  小肯
I did know his son, Ken Jr.
- 你俩是朋友吗  - 和小肯吗  不是
- Oh, and you were friends? - With Ken Jr.? No.
你知道的  我们了解彼此  但是他在大一的时候就死了
You know, we knew each other but he died freshman year of college.
用药过量
Overdosed.
这个家庭经历的太多
The family's been through so much.
听着  我的意思是  如果你想今晚就这样了
Oh. Well, listen, I mean, if you want to call it a night,
我意思是  我明白的
I mean, I understand.
你都打扮好了
Well, you are all dressed up.
你还穿着你的黑鞋子
And you wore your black shoes.
- 是啊  - 我打赌你的袜子也很般配
- I did. - I bet your socks even match.
他们确实是
They do.
我们或许应该找点事情做
Maybe we should just get something to go.
回你那边去
Head back to your place.
好的  你可以  呃  确保把我衣服挂对地方
All right. You can, uh, make sure I hang up my suit correctly.
好
Okay.
需要什么帮忙吗
Can I help you?
我来这整理阿尔文的办公室
I'm here to fix up Alvin's office.
什么
Excuse me?
我来这整理艾尔文的办公室
I'm here to fix up Alvin's office.
比利  这是露露的办公室
Oh, hey, Billy. Uh, this is Lulu's office now.
我的办公室在别的地方
My omice is somewhere else.
- 艾米丽  - 伯恩斯利
- Ah. Emily, uh... - Bernsley.
艾米丽  这是比利·汉森
Emily, this is Billy Henson.
来吧我们走  比利
Come on. Let's go, Billy.
我需要一个扶手
Uh, I'm gonna need a hand rail.
我希望你能帮我做一些小的文件柜和书架
And I was hoping you'd build me some smaller filing cabinets and bookshelves.
- 低一点  - 对对  低一点
- Lower? - Yeah, yeah, lower.
今天早上我接到刑事法庭的电话
I got a call this morning from the criminal courts.
他们想让安德鲁去看心理医生
They want Andrew evaluated by a psychiatrist.
- 什么时候测试  - 今天下午一刻钟
- When's the test?- Quarter past one this afternoon.
西南精神少年科
The Juvenile Wing of Southwestern Psych.
- 好的  谢谢  - 好的
- All right. Thanks. - Okay.
我也可以降低灯的开关  如果你想的话
I can lower the light switches, too, if you want.
为什么不呢
Why not?
- 比利  - 怎么了
- Billy? - Yeah?
警察那边什么情况
How did it go with the police?
他们还是一直问关于我爸爸的事情
They just kept asking about my dad.
- 好吧  - 关于他怎么死的
- Right. - About how he died.
他怎么死的
How did he die?
他在三年前被刺伤了
He got stabbed about three years ago.
他们一直问我我觉得是怎么发生的  我觉得是谁做的
They kept asking what I thought happened and who I thought did it.
- 他们从来没找到凶手吗  - 他们从来没有
- They never found the killer? - No, they never did.
他们需要了解我什么
What do they need to know about me?
那个医生只是希望看看  有没有什么原因让你记不起来
The doctor just wants to see if there's a reason you can't remember
你被袭击的那晚发生了什么
what happened the night you were attacked.
我只是想不起来
I just can't remember.
好的
Right.
但是你确实在医院和警方说了什么
But you did say something to the police in the hospital.
这就是地区检察官想和你谈的事
That's what the District Attorney wants to talk to you about.
我对警方说过的话吗
What I said to the police?
好吧
Right.
我不记得我说过什么了
I don't remember what I said.
这就是为什么法官要你和医生谈谈
That's why the judge wants you to talk to the doctor.
可能我不用去作证了吗
So maybe I don't have to testify?
可能吧
Maybe.
先生  我能帮你吗
Sir, can I help you?
- 抱歉  你不能回来  - 别挡我的路  女士
- I'm sorry, you can't come back here. - Get out of my way, lady.
阿尔文  阿尔文
Alvin? Alvin?
查尔斯
Charles?
Charles.
太晚了  查尔斯
It's too late, Charles.
我要我的文件  阿尔文
I need my files, Alvin.
我从来没有给我的未婚妻  说我继父对我做了什么
I never told my fiancée what my step-father did to me.
从来没有告诉任何人
Never told nobody.
现在这些警察来拜访我和我谈论这些事情
Now the cops are coming around to talk to me about it.
她还想知道是怎么回事儿
And she wants to know what's going on.
还有两周我就要和这个女人结婚了
I'm marrying this woman in two weeks.
我告诉她发生了什么  她会怎么说
What's she gonna say when I tell her what happened?
如果这事公开了  我要起诉你  阿尔文
lf this comes out in public, I'm suing your ass, Alvin.
我会找你的事儿的
I'm gonna come after you.
照顾好你自己吧  比利
Take care of yourself, Billy.
嗨  比利
Hi, Billy.
我  我  做了这个  刚刚做好
l--l made this, just now.
在找威廉·海森
Looking for William Henson.
他就在那后面
Oh, he's, uh, right back there.
比利
Billy?
德马里亚警探  我们昨天讲过话
Detective DeMaria. We spoke yesterday.
我  我记得
Yeah, l--l remember.
我希望你能到警局  来和我们再谈谈
I was hoping you'd come down to the station and talk with us again.
- 为什么  - 我们还有点问题
- Why? - We have some more questions.
- 比利是嫌疑人吗  - 你是他的律师吗
- Is Billy a suspect? - Are you his lawyer?
是的  我劝他不要跟你说话
Yes. I'm advising him not to talk to you.
- 那你应该安排他保释  - 你要逮捕他
- Then you should arrange his bail. - You arresting him?
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
什么都别回答
Don't answer any questions.
好吧  阿尔文
It's all right, Alvin.
什么都别说  比利
Don't answer any questions, Billy.
你有权和一名律师讲话
You have the right to speak to an attorney.
如果你不能得到一个  政府将派个一给你
lf you cannot amord one, one will be appointed to you at government expense.
你明白我刚才向你解释的权力了吗
You understand these rights as I've explained them to you?
好了
Okay.
怎么样
How did it go?
打扰了  你有空吗
Uh, excuse me. Do you have a minute?
坐着等会儿
Just take a seat.
呃  你有什么发现
Uh, what did you find?
考虑到目前的情况 安德鲁的身体状况似乎还不错
Andrew seems to be functioning well, given the circumstances.
他很清楚真相和谎言的区别
He definitely understands the dimerence between truth and lies.
你认为这里有生理和心理上的原因吗
Do you think there's any psychological/physical reasons
为什么他记不起来发生过什么
why he can't remember what happened?
我的观点是否定的
ln my opinion, no.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
抱歉  我刚刚
Sorry, I was just--
这些文件跟你没有任何关系
That file's none of your business.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我  我  对不起
l, uh...I'm sorry.
- 他们让他出来了吗  - 没有
- Did they let him out? - Uh, no.
他的传讯要到明早了
His arraignment isn't until tomorrow morning.
- 他怎么样  - 不知道
- How's he doing? - Don't know.
他们不让我见他
They wouldn't let me see him.
我想你是他的律师吧
I thought you were his lawyer?
我是这么说的  但是比利并没有要求见我
Yeah, I said I was, but Billy didn't ask for me.
就是
It's just...
我的意思是  很明显警察他做了这些事
I mean, clearly the police think that he's doing these--
不   他们逮捕他的理由是流放  而不是谋杀
No. They arrested him for an outstanding vagrancy warrant, not for the killings.
他们为什么这样做啊
Why would they do that?
他们想就这些枪击事件审问他
They want to interrogate him about these shootings,
他们试图恐吓他
and they're trying to intimidate him.
我看了他的文件
I read his files.
我知道
I know.
他爸爸对他做的事情
Things his father did to him.
你觉得这可能是是他做的吗
You think he could be doing it?
比利  不可能
Billy? No.
我不知道
I don't know.
不可能
No.
警方逮捕了一个与最近枪击案有关
Police have arrested a 29-year-old man
的29岁男性
in relation to the recent shootings.
威廉·海森  一个从南边来的杂工
William Henson, a handyman from the South Side,
警方给他看了未执行的逮捕证之后
confessed to the killings late last night
他对对昨晚的谋杀供认不讳
after police brought him in on an outstanding warrant.
其他新闻  有更严重的火灾警报
ln other news, a greater alarm fire
在南边  火警部门持续忙碌
on the South Side kept fire departments busy.
就这些
So this is it.
所以你会去证人席就坐
You'll be seated on the witness stand.
地方检察官会问你问题
The District Attorney will be asking you questions.
他会问什么样的问题
What kind of questions is he gonna ask?
他会问你对那晚还记得什么
He's gonna ask you what you remember about the night.
但是我什么都不记得
But I don't remember anything.
地方检察官不会信的
The District Attorney is not gonna believe that.
给你做检查的精神科医生也不会相信的
And the psychiatrist that examined you doesn't believe it.
他们还会问我什么问题
What other questions are they gonna ask me?
你那天干什么了  你晚饭吃了什么
What you did that day. What you had for dinner.
你什么时候上床睡觉了
What time you went to bed.
好吧
Right.
你记得什么吗
Do you remember any of that?
我们吃了通心粉的奶酪
We had macaroni and cheese.
我去做作业了  然后我睡觉了
I did my homework and I went to sleep.
所以他想知道为什么你记得所有事情
So he'll want to know why you can remember all of that
却不记得被袭击了
but you can't remember being attacked.
安德鲁  在法庭外撒谎是一回事
Andrew, it's one thing to lie outside of the courtroom.
在席位上撒谎是另外一回事
It's another thing to lie on the stand.
你觉得我在撒谎吗
You think I'm lying?
我知道你在撒谎
I know you're lying.
我只是希望你没有
I just wish you wouldn't.
我没有撒谎
I'm not lying.
但是你记得那晚你吃了通心粉和奶酪
But you remember you had macaroni and cheese for dinner that night?
是的
Yes.
而且你在你的卧室做了作业
And that you did your homework in your room.
对
Yeah.
十点你去睡觉了
That you went to bed at 10:00.
是的
Yeah.
然后接下来发生的事情你不记得了
And you just don't remember what happened next.
我醒来就在医院了
I woke up in the hospital.
你确定你不记得在你去医院之前发生了什么吗
You sure you don't remember what happened before you got to the hospital?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
安德鲁  你记得你的手和胳膊是怎么受伤的吗
Andrew, do you remember how you got those cuts on your hands and arms?
不记得
No.
你不记得和谁在你卧室打起来了吗
You don't remember fighting someone om in your bedroom?
我不记得
I don't remember.
你的你告诉警察有人在你的房间吗
You remember telling the police about someone being in your room?
- 不记得  - 康诺利先生
- No. - Mr. Connolly!
当你采访这个证人时
When you interviewed this witness,
他指认被告是攻击他的人吗
did he name the defendant as his attacker?
没有
No.
但是现在你希望他会在证人席上说出他的名字
But now you're hoping he'll suddenly name him on the witness stand?
他告诉警察有一个男性在他卧室袭击他了
He told the police that a man attacked him in his bedroom
而且那个袭击者告诉他不要告诉任何人
and that the attacker told him not to tell anyone.
安德鲁  你说这些了吗
Andrew, did you say that?
我不记得
I don't remember.
谢谢你  安德鲁  你可以下去了
Thank you, Andrew. You can step down.
我需要撤销这些指控
I'm dismissing these charges.
不是现在
Not now, please.
所以我现在能回家了吗
So I can go home now?
什么
What?
安德鲁  我们什么都做不了  除非你帮我们
Andrew, there's nothing more we can do to help you unless you help us.
好吗
All right?
如果你需要什么打电话给我
Call me if you need anything.
我们很高兴孩子回来了  这是我一生中最美好的一天  真的
We're thrilled to have our kid back. It's just the best day of my life, really.
约翰
John!
把武器放下
Put the weapon down!
别开枪  别拿枪对着他
Don't shoot him! Don't shoot him!
放下手里的武器
Drop the weapon!
约翰  放下它  约翰
John! Put it down, John.
求求你了  约翰  把枪放下
Please, John. Put the gun down.
求求你了  约翰  约翰  不要 不要这样  约翰
Oh, please, John! John! Don't--don't do that, John.
约翰  约翰  我能帮你
John. John, I can help you.
让我来帮你
Let me help you.
- 不  -  拜托让我帮你吧
- No. - Please let me help.
这些都无所谓了  马斯特森先生
It doesn't matter any more, Mr. Masterson.
约翰  你有可爱的孩子  妻子  你不能
John, you have a beautiful child, a wife. You can't--
这些都不重要了
It doesn't matter any more.
约翰
John.
- 阿尔文  我们太担心了  - 我没事
- Oh, Alvin, we were so worried. - I'm fine.
警方有好多问题  但是我没事
Police had a bunch of questions, but I'm fine.
好吧  为什么不回家休息一会儿
Well, why don't you go home and get some rest?
我们在这都能得到照应
We've got everything covered here.
- 我没事  露露  - 你确定
- I'm all right, Lulu. - Are you sure?
我无敌的很
I'm invincible.
- 艾尔文  - 有任何关于安德鲁·福特的消息吗
- Alvin. - Any news on Andrew Ford?
没有
No.
好吧  我听警察局说了这件事
Well, I heard about it at the police station.
他们派了很多人去找他
They've got a lot of people out looking for him.
阿尔文
Yeah. Alvin, wh--
怎么了
What?
你怎么想的
What were you thinking?
- 我怎么想的  - 对
- What was I thinking? - Yeah.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
守灵怎么样
How was the wake?
好难过
It was sad.
鉴于现在所有出来的消息  我是说
And given everything that's come out since, I mean...
人们不知道会怎么想格雷厄姆先生
People just don't know what to think about Mr. Graham,
现在他们说凶手是热心市民
now that they're saying his killer was a vigilante.
是的
Right.
我只是痛恨在小肯身上发生的事
I just hate to think that's what happened to Ken, Jr.
但我干这行太久了  不会错过细节的
But I've been in this business too long to miss the signs.
我的意思是  小肯是个典型的虐待儿童的案例
I mean, Ken, Jr. was a textbook case of child abuse.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
毒品   辍学  搬家
Well, the drugs, the failing out of school, the moving around.
但是你不认为是他自己选择去做这些事的吗
But don't you think he... chose to do those things?
我不认为
No.
但你是通过一个人如何受害来定义他的生活的
But you're defining someone's life by how they were victimized.
受害者喜欢这些  这会改变人的
Being victimized like that, it changes people.
这改变了他们
It changes them.
如果钱不是问题
lf money were no object--
什么
Excuse me?
如果钱不是问题  你想去哪工作
lf money were no object, where would you work?
在这儿还是法林&法林律所
Here or at Fallin & Fallin?
法林&法林律所
Fallin & Fallin.
或者就这里
Or maybe here.
真的吗
Really?
这地方很重要
Well, this place matters.
事实上客户需要他们  人们在这真的为客户做了些好事
People here do very good work for clients that actually need them.
但是钱是个问题
But money is an object.
安德鲁
Andrew.
你去哪了
Where have you been?
我记得
I remember.
有个孩子  特洛伊
There's this kid, Troy,
住在我家街上
who lives down my street.
好
Right.
他在高中里
He's in high school.
我和他弟弟戴夫是朋友
I'm friends with his little brother Dave.
安德鲁  你想让我打电话给你妈妈吗
Andrew, do you want me to call your mother?
让我说完
Let me finish.
那天夜里发生的
The night it happened,
我和罗伊
me...and Troy...
还有戴夫
and Dave
在我房间里玩电动游戏
were playing video games in my room.
然后我打败了特洛伊   连着六次
And I beat Troy, like, six times in a row...
因为我很擅长玩那个游戏
'cause I'm good at the game.
特洛伊袭击了你
Did Troy attack you?
因为这个游戏
Because of the game?
为什么
Why?
晚些的时候特洛伊过来了
Troy came over, later that night.
我的意思是
I mean...
我邀请他过来的
I invited him over.
然后我们又开始玩这个游戏了
And we started playing the game again.
我让他赢了
And I let him win.
然后我告诉他  我们可以一起做些别的
And I told him we could do some other stuff...together.
好的
Right.
然后我们做了
And we did.
好的
Right.
然后特洛伊
And Troy...
之后
after...
特洛伊真的生气了
Troy was really mad.
他说这些以后都不会发生了
He said it never happened.
他是真的生气了
He was really mad.
特洛伊不想我告诉我任何人
Troy didn't want me to tell anybody.
- 阿尔文在他办公室吗  - 是的
- Is Alvin in his office?- Yes.
比利  谢谢花的事儿
Billy, thanks for the flower.
这只是些旧木头
It was just some old wood.
谢谢
Thanks.
我过来收尾
I came to finish up.
这工作收费多少
What's the job pay again?
每年$31,000  加上福利
$31,000 annually, plus benefits.
一年需要接多少案子
And how many cases would I have to take a year?
大概300-400起案子
Probably 300-400.
你打算什么时候休产假
And what's your plan for when you take maternity leave?
说实话  我不知道
Uh, honestly, I have no idea.
听起来不太好  是吗
Doesn't sound too good, does it?
是不太好
It doesn't.
我接受这份工作
I'll take the job.
我和查尔斯谈过了
I talked to Charles.
他说他和他未婚妻说过了  他说进展的都还不错
He said he told his fiancée. He said it went all right.
你们  呃
You guys, uh...
你们说了很多
You guys talk a lot?
我们会聊
We talk.
你为什么告诉警方是你干的
Why did you tell the police you did it?
好吧  他们一直在说我做了  或者是我  我想做
Well, they kept saying I did it or l--l wanted to do it.
你知道怎么了吗  阿尔文
And you know what, Alvin?
我想是我杀了这些人
I kinda wish I did kill those guys.
我希望是我做的
I wish I did.
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177